{
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "question": "What vehicles did the Empire use in its assault on the rebels' Hoth base?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Snowspeeders",
        "TIE Fighters",
        "AT-ATs",
        "TIE Bombers"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who infiltrated Jabba's palace dressed as a bounty hunter named Boushh?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Luke Skywalker",
        "Lando Calrissian",
        "Chewbacca",
        "Princess Leia"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who first discovered stormtroopers on Cloud City but couldn't tell his friends?",
      "choices":
      [
        "R2-D2",
        "Chewbacca",
        "Han Solo",
        "C-3PO"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "How many forms of communication does C-3PO speak?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Over 6 million",
        "Over 6,000",
        "Over 3 million",
        "Over 3,000"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the pit droid did Jar Jar have to hit to get it to stop acting up?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Head",
        "Belly",
        "Nose",
        "Back"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of droid is R2-D2?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Roomba",
        "Astromech",
        "Unknown",
        "Protocol"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many lightsabers does General Grievous use?",
      "choices":
      [
        "One",
        "Six",
        "Four",
        "Two"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What command was given to turn the clones to the dark side?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Order 26",
        "Order 56",
        "Order 6",
        "Order 66"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was Anakin Skywalker born?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Tatooine",
        "Coruscant",
        "Endor",
        "Naboo"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many Jedi are on the Jedi Council?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Ten",
        "Twelve",
        "Sixteen",
        "Eight"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Senator from Alderaan?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Bail Organa",
        "Ask Ask",
        "Padme Amidala",
        "MI Lo"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which ship does Wedge pilot in Return of the Jedi?",
      "choices":
      [
        "A-Wing",
        "X-Wing",
        "B-Wing",
        "Millennium Falcon"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the creature that swallows and spits out R2-D2 in the Dagobah system?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Jaws",
        "Wampah",
        "Bigfoot",
        "Dragonsnake"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does AT-AT stand for?",
      "choices":
      [
        "All Terrain Armoured Transport",
        "Attack Terrain Armoured Transport",
        "Auto Transport Attack Tank",
        "Another Tight Armoured Transporter"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the only non-Jedi/Sith in the trilogy to use a lightsaber?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Leia",
        "Han Solo",
        "Chewbacca",
        "R2-D2"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "C-3PO gives Han some odds regarding the successful navigation of an asteroid field. what were the odds?",
      "choices":
      [
        "3,722,000 to 1",
        "45,572 to 1",
        "3,720 to 1",
        "2,500 to 1"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is in charge of the Empire's ground attack on Hoth?",
      "choices":
      [
        "General Veers",
        "Grand Moff Tarkin",
        "Darth Vader",
        "Captain Needs"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the Wampa's arms did Luke slice off in Empire Strikes Back?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Left arm",
        "Right arm",
        "Both arms",
        "None"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which villain was NOT a member of the Separatist Council?",
      "choices":
      [
        "General Grievous",
        "Count Dooku",
        "Darth Maul",
        "Viceroy Nute Gunray"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who took more than half of Anakin Skywalker's arm during battle?",
      "choices":
      [
        "Darth Vader",
        "Count Dooku",
        "General Grievous",
        "Darth Maul"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}